Guide to the Mab Segrest Papers, 1889-2014 RL.01164
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Activism, 1969-2014; 30 boxes
  - North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence (NCARRV), 1985-1993
    - Ms Foundation, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - RAC labels & addresses, undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - National YWCA, undated (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Jewish community issues, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Anti-gay violence, my stuff, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Adrienne reading, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - The Murder of Joyce Sinclair special report, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - NCARRV board, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - NCARRV youth project, 1990-1991 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - NCARRV conference, undated (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - North Carolinians Against Racist & Religious Violence publications, undated (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Raleigh hearings, undated (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (NCCGLE), 1991-1995
    - NCCGLE to dos, 1991-1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Homophobia and human rights in North Carolina, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - NCCGLE, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - NCCGLE notes, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - NCCGLE stationary, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Organizer's manual: Blow the Whistle on Anti-Gay and Lesbian Violence, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Resource Center, 1983-1992 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian and Gay Health Project, NCCGLE, 1983-1991 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - NCCGLE grants, budgets, 1983-1992 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Homophobic Violence Project, 1984-1991 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - NCCGLE consulting: minutes & project notes, 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - NCCGLE publications, 1990 (Box 132, Folder 9, 10)
    - Alternative Resources of the Triad (ART) material, hotline, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Ben & Jerry's Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Conference call, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - NCCGLE documentation project, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - NCCGLE expenses & finances, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - NCCGLE grants, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - NCCGLE legal, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - NCCGLE board notes, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - NCCGLE grants, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Report release, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Southern community partners, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Out Fund, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - National contacts, undated (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - NCCGLE publications, undated (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Office, undated (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - WomonWrites, 1980-1985
    - WomonWrites, 1980-1982 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - WomonWrites racism task force, 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - WomonWrites manual, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - WomonWrites lists, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Southern Exposure: words from WomonWrites, 1983 (Box 80)
    - WomonWrites anthology, 1985 (Box 80)
  - Our South, 1980-1982
    - Project notes: Our South, 1980-1982 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Feminary, 1969-1982
    - Research Triangle Women's Liberation newsletter, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Feminist newsletter, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2, 3)
    - A Feminary, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 4, 5)
    - Feminary minutes, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Feminary/south, first cover art, Sue Sheddon, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Feminary minutes and correspondence, 1974-1992 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Feminary retreat, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Feminary & Womanwrites mailing lists, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Feminary v. 8, nos. 1-2, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Feminary v. 8, no. 3 & v. 9, no. 1, 1977-1978 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Feminary, v. 10, nos. 1-2, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Feminary v. 11, nos. 1-2, 1980-1981 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Feminary, v. 11, no. 3 & v. 12, no. 1, 1981-1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR), 1986-1997
    - Center for Democratic Renewal pamphlets, 1986-1989 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - CDR, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Quarantines & Death: The Far Right's Homophobic Agenda, CDR, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - CDR memos, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - CDR, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Militia, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - CDR, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Board meetings & minutes, 1988-1991 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Clips, CDR, 1988-1989 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - CDR, 1989-1990 (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
    - CDR Axum personnel, undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - CDR audit, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - CDR current, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 6, 7)
    - CDR retreat, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Finances, CDR, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Homophobia and anti-fascist strategy, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - NW office, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Personnel policies - current, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Proposals, CDR, 1988-1990 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - CDR background, 1981-1991 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR) northwest office, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - The Monitor (CDR Publication), 1987 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly reports, Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR), 1987-1990 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR) documents related to Blakeley, GA incident, 1990 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - CDR personnel, 1990-1991 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR) staff and volunteer handbook, 1990 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR), 1993-1994 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR) publications, undated (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Center for Democratic Renewal (CDR): rural right training material, undated (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Race syllabus, undated (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - National Women's Studies Association/Southeastern Women's Studies Association (NWSA/SEWSA), 1987-1988
    - NWSA membership directory, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - NWSA talk, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - NWSA 88 proposal, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - SEWSA talk, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - SEWSA, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - White fem/white sym, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Women's Studies Association (SEWSA) annual meeting, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - World Council of Churches/Urban Rural Mission (WCC/URM), 1992-1999
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - We Are the Ones We Have Been Waiting For (Urban-Rural Mission), 1995 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Annual report: Urban-Rural Mission (USA), 1999 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Sexuality globally, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - World Council of Churches assembly, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Journeys Toward Wholeness, Revised Lifelines, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Lifelines: final submitted, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Lifelines: Journeys of Sex and the Spirit, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Notebook: URM, undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Treasure in an Earthen Vessel & The Gospel and The Colony of Puerto Rico, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Urban-Rural Mission (USA) background documents, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Transcript of interview with Jean Hardisty, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Bifocal publication, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky Foundation for Women, 1990
    - Kentucky Foundation proposal, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Kentucky Foundation for Women proposal, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Narratives of Slavery… draft, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Kentucky Foundation for Women, undated (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - War Resisters League, 1979-1981
    - War Resisters League, 1979-1981 (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
  - Conferences, 1986-2014
    - Pride, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Carl's piece, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - West Coast Old Lesbian Conference & Celebration, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Ithaca, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Santa Cruz, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Yale, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Iowa conference, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Blue Mountain, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Iowa City papers, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Material from Windcall activism retreat, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Regional Economic Justice Network, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Windcall, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Dialogue on the lesbian and gay left, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Highlander, 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Pamela Overeynder, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Learning Spanish/gay, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Pride, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - The Making and Unmaking of Whiteness, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Ninth Annual Duke University Women's Studies Graduate Research conference, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Leadership at the Crossroads, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - University of Alabama, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Newcomb conf., 2007 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - SSSL Panel Conference, 2014 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Archival conference for Southern women writers, 1987-1990 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Leaven workshop, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Southeast social forum, 2003-2008 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Association of Women's Music & Culture (AWMAC), undated (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Women's Project gathering, undated (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1986-2004
    - "The Beginning of a Farewell": eulogy for Carl Whitman, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Stonewall speech, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Independent forum on race relations remarks, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - King address, Greensboro College, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - ML King speech, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - SAMLA talk, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - "The Dangers of Right-Wing Feminism," I Am Your Sister conference, Boston, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Delaware workshop, 1990-1992 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Southern History conference, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Time's Witness, 1991-1992 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - National Network of Grantmakers plenary on democracy, 1992 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Creating Change speech, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - NGLTF Creating Change speech, Durham, NC, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Building Bridges, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - UVA, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Keynote address by Mab Segrest, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Unitarian speech, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Am 2 decision, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Reid College, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Republican Convention piece, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - What's Love…, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - "Going to the Chapel", 1997 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - UNC, "More Speech: Gay/Marriage, Academic/Freedom, & Other Oxymorons," in response to controversy in Crystal's diss., 2004 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut College, undated (Box 94, Folder 24, 25)
    - Cornell talk, undated (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - "Freedom Means Everybody," Duke/Bingham Center, undated (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - FSC speech, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - "Going to the Chapel", undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Homophobia and Women's Studies, undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Louisville, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Louisville speech, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Marta's prayer, undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Nec. Bread/NY speech, disarm demo, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - No Easy Walk, undated (Box 95, Folder 8, 9)
    - Racism discussion group notes, undated (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Right-wing feminism speech, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Rutgers, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - SAMLA talk, undated (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - SELGC keynote, undated (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - SLGC speech, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Speech, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - "Spiritual Warfare", undated (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Tacoma, undated (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Talk/Connecticut/sex, undated (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Unitarian, undated (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - University of Delaware, undated (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - University of Florida, undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - UNC, undated (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - UNC Women's Studies, undated (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - UVA, undated (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Vermont, undated (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - Women, risk, & faith, undated (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Coming Out talk, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Letter and copy of lecture from Adrienne Rich to Mab, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Speaking engagements, undated (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Various Groups, 1974-2010
    - TALF and other lesbians, 1974-1978 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Radical feminist organizing material, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Poverty in N.C., 1985 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Hollow corporation, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Speaking engagement, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - RNEW, 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Sher's NCAE piece on N.C., 1988 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Turning Point working manual, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - United Way scan, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Annie Ellman, 1989-2004 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Southerners for Economic Justice, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Gay/lesbian, 1990-1993 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - NGLTF report, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Giard, 1991-1995 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Southeast Regional Economic Justice Network, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Amnesty International gay material, 1993-1995 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - HIV, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - National Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality, 1993-1999 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Speak Out, 1994-1995 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Unitarian Universalist Association (UUA), 1994-2001 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - New Era, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - NGLTF/affirmative action, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Center for Development in Central America (CDCA), 1996 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Welfare, 1995-1996 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Durham: women, 1996-1998 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Jubilee, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Family matters, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Info. about poverty, health care, and Medicare, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Welfare Information, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Durham County: Work First county plan model, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Post-Gay, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Speak Out, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - All Souls Church, Unitarian Universalist, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Farm labor organizing committee, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - National Center for Human Rights Education, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Atlanta Transformative Justice Collaborative (ATL TJC), 2007-2010 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Feminist Vision Award, Agnes Scott College, 2009-2010 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Abstinence until marriage, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Anti-CAN, undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Arkansas project, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - The Backlash Book, undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Center for Research on Women proposal, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Culture Wars/NEA, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Funding sources, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Grant stuff, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Greater Cleveland roundtable, undated (Box 99, Folder 9, 10)
    - Jewish women vs. occupation, undated (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Marie Oakley/SEJ Southerners for Econ. Justice, undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Center for Research on Women, undated (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - NGLTF (National Gay and Lesbian Task Force), undated (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - NGTF: Kevin, undated (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Nicaragua, witness for peace delegation, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 16, Box 136, Folder 6)
    - NOVA, undated (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - PASE, Girls NC/Action for Safety, Annie Ellman, undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Proof sheet, NGLTF song, birth connection, undated (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Race and spirit/Mark, undated (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Request to NGLTF for PD organizer to work on Senate race v. Helms, Anti-Helms Race, undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Sherover-Marcuse, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Harvey Jackins, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Social Justice Empowerment Program, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Southern Echo, Inc., undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Two "How Democracy Works" pamphlets, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Tyrell, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Warren County protests, undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Welfare reform bill in NC, undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Mab deposition: Robert L. Percell vs. International Business Machines, Inc., 1994 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - NC Arts Council proposal draft, undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Arts Council Program, 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Activist political buttons, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 101, 102)
    - FEMA scramble, undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Levee Policy Creole, undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Marshland Souffle, undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Recipes for Transformation, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - NEH summer seminar for college teachers, 1983-1984 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - NEH grant, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Religious Network for Equality for Women (RNEW), 1988 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Iowa conference, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Lesbian agenda conference, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Religious Network for Equality for Women, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - SAMLA "Southern Writers Writers, Southern Publishers" panel, 1989 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, Creating Change conference, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Racism workshop, National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - IDC presentation, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Shake Loose Our Skin: A Celebration of the 20th Anniversary of the Zale Writer-in-Residence Program, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Anti-Racism workshop led by Mab Segrest, undated (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - "Miscegenating Canons, Queering Texts," Symposium on Contemporary Southern Literature, undated (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Training, undated (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Workshop materials, undated (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Workshop on colonialism and racism, undated (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Religious Network for Equality for Women (RNEW), 1987-1991 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Duke-UNC Center for Research on Women application, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Majority People's Fund (MPF) materials, 1994-1995 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - David Duke, undated (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - David Duke material, undated (Box 136, Folder 11, Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Marriage Project - Hawaii, undated (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Nazi homophobia chronology, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - A second open letter to southern white women, by Anne Braden, undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - The Women's Project Watchcare Network, undated (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Video script, undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Activist Publications, 1978-2000
    - Gay baiting, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 1, Box 105, Folder 14)
    - VA Tech, 1978-1985 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - From Fear to Joy: Anti-Klan Work in NC, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Marcy Adelman, Ph.D., 1987 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Various newsletters, 1992-1995 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Fight the Right, 1993 (Box 104)
    - Lesbian women, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Astraea, 1994-1995 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Expert witness, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - 4WCW, 1995-2001 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - In These Times, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - News and Observer, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 13, 14)
    - The Point, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - University of Delaware, 1995-1996 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Am 2 Decision newspaper articles, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Clinton, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - The Conservatism of the Heart, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Mothers' Voice Press conference, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper article, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Notebook, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - The Republican Platform, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - San Diego, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Linguafranca, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Newsweek, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Hate Violence Art, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - February, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - The Public Eye, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Anti-racist pedagogy, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - B. Deming article for Southern Exposure (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Clips, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Deadly Connections information packet, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Flyer for Antonovich murder, produced with Allan & Carl, undated (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Gaybaiting: Anatomy of an Election article, undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - NC Independent, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Nicaragua, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Original recall, Anti-Discrim Week proclamation, Wib Gulley, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Origins of Post-Modernity, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Our Own Place, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Readings on feminism & non-violence, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Reagan, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Recall, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Research on citizens' councils, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Time is money, undated (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Readings on feminism & non-violence, undated (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - WomanSpirit, 1978-1980 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Mother Jones AIDS article by Randy Shilts, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Southerners for Economic Justice, 1989-1990 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Electoral politics/Durham, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence, undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Free speech articles, undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Gays and the military, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Information on Judge Robert Bork from the ACLU, undated (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Multicultural, undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force reports, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Porn debates, undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Witness for Peace, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Research and Subject Files, 1918-2005; 10 boxes
  The Research and Subject Files series contains printed material as well as interviews, some of which were conducted by Dr. Segrest as part of her research for her published works.
  - Printed Materials, 1918-2005
    - Iris: A Journal About Women, 1988-1989 (Box 107)
    - Organized Women Divided, Heresies #9, 1980 (Box 107)
    - Chrysalis, 1978 (Box 107)
    - Southern Exposure, Encyclopedia of Southern Life & Change, 1983 (Box 107)
    - Outlook: National Lesbian & Gay Quarterly, 1988 (Box 107)
    - 10 Percent Magazine, undated (Box 107)
    - A Small pain, by Flyin' Thunda Cloud, 1986 (Box 107)
    - Gossip, A Journal of Lesbian Feminist Ethics, 1986 (Box 107)
    - The Drumbeat of Life: Jubilee in an African Context, by Sebastian Bakare, 1997 (Box 107)
    - A Community of Clowns: Testimonies of People in Urban Rural Mission, compiled by Hugh Lewin, 1987 (Box 107)
    - Padre Mac: The Man from Harris, undated (Box 107)
    - Sign Language, by Monica Raymond, 1978 (Box 107)
    - Trivia: A Journal of Ideas, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Echoes of the Bell Witch in the Twentieth Century, 1979 (Box 107)
    - Who Was That Masked Woman? A Novel, by Noretta Koertge, 1981 (Box 107)
    - In the Presence of Mine Enemies: An American Chaplain in World War II German Prison Camps, by Chaplain (Major) Eugene L. Daniel, Jr. (AUS-Retired), 1985 (Box 107)
    - Court document, 1988 (Box 110)
    - Expose: The Journal of Interdisciplinary Inquiry, 2006 (Box 108)